So, this is obviously big surprise. It
is uh 9/11, which is big day. Big day
for some people.
Uh Muslim man shouts Allahu Akbar
outside in New York City City Hall on
the 25th anniversary OF 9/11.
MAN.
>> [gasps and laughter]
>> JESUS CHRIST. And uh it's it's insane,
bro. Like these people are savage. Like
they're yelling at each other, being
again. And this is like it's a New York
City firefighter just unloaded on
pro-Palestine activists in an Elmo
costume. What is this? I'll watch I'll
just watch it.
Man.
Dressed like a clown, too. I
love it.
Patriot Yeah, if you like the country so
much, leave. Get the out. And uh
yeah, don't forget our Palestinians
cheered in the streets after 9/11. This
is true, by the way. A lot of the uh a
lot of people in Palestine cheered on
9/11.
And [snorts] uh people forget about
that.
A 9/11 widow just went rogue on New York
City. Uh-oh.
>> And my husband, Tom Strada.
>> Wait, oh, this just happened. Oh,
>> You are missed more with each year that
passes, but how can it be 25 years and
still [music] we have no justice for the
role that Saudi Arabia played in your
murder.
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> Yes, we finally made it into a court and
have proved that the Kingdom of Saudi
Arabia fomented a rancid culture of
anti-American terrorism around the globe
and then sent its agents
>> They had oil, yeah. Their parades? Oh,
I'm sure.
>> But for 25 years, administration after
administration, including leaders in
front of us here today, chose to protect
the Saudis instead of standing with the
9/11 families.
>> Man.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> Man.
>> They withheld evidence. They vetoed
JASTA.
They broke promises,
>> It's a lot.
>> public and private. It has been one
betrayal after another.
>> Music's loud. I I can't turn it off.
It's just
>> Trump can still change that. Tell the
Saudis to stop lying. Tell them that if
they want to be friends with the USA,
they cannot continue to deny all of
this, all of the pain, all of the
destruction that we have all been
suffering.
>> presidents are all there. Oh, boy.
>> Thank you for being here today.
>> Mhm. [cheering]
>> Please, carry that message back.
Stand with the families.
Stand with the survivors. Stand with
Americans. As my husband, Tom, would
have said, that is always the right
thing to do.
>> Uh-huh.
>> God bless all of us. God bless America.
>> Jesus, man. Yeah. And uh in case you're
wondering, these are 9/11 records about
the lawsuit widows sought it. Yeah,
there's more of this year. Two Saudi
government employees made of service an
advanced team for the hijackers. Yeah,
there was like a huge thing about this.
Let me go to the other ones, too. Never
forgive, never forget. Yeah, what was
the one more? AOC and Mamdani seen
laughing together as the names of the
honored dead are read at Ground Zero.
>> Ramana Lachhman
>> Ganesh K Ladkat
>> James Patrick Ladley
>> Man.
>> Lachhman
>> Ganesh K Ladkat
>> It doesn't look good. I'll tell you
that. It really doesn't look good. And
cuz they don't care. Well, I mean, it's
pretty obvious that I mean, very clearly
a lot of people that were from these
other parts of the world, like they
wanted 9/11 to happen. They were happy
that 9/11 happened.
Like there's tons of videos of people
cheering and celebrating 9/11 happening.
So,
a wild hubbub, yeah. And they're not
American? No, they're not. I've said
this before, right? Scroll the word sort
of 5 hours ago. Yeah, no, and this is
it. So, for me, let me find Let me see
if I can find it here. Where the hell
did it go? And yeah, this is it.
It's kind of crazy this was 25 years
ago.
It really is. Like it's actually wild
this was 25 years ago when it
happened. Because I remember So, I was
in
Where is it here? I scroll all the way
down and go through these, right? And I
was in history class in sixth grade.
And I remember it happened and I was
just like, oh, is this like yeah, let me
let me actually go all the way down.
There's so there might be some reposts
here, so it might take me a minute to
just catch all of them.
Okay. Um
Yeah. And didn't the three princes of
Saudi Arabia What is this here? And died
very weirdly. I have no idea. And they
wheeled in the TVs, bro. Yeah, I
remember like somebody came in, I think
somebody came into the uh
what do you call it? They came into the
room or the TV turned on or something
like that and we started watching it and
I remember like kids were calling their
parents and everybody was totally
freaking out. I remember my teacher was
crying and I was just like wait, what
the Like and like other teachers
came into the room and they were talking
to each other. I was like shocked, man.
Yeah, I was on chat. Yeah, everybody was
watching this, right? Everybody was
there and yeah, school was canceled in
Arizona. Well, I remember when it
happened,
basically class was pretty much over for
the rest of the day. Well, everybody
just sat there and watched the news.
Like the entire the entire school, like
every classroom, every school, every you
know, like teacher was just watching the
news and watching this happen. It was
like not even about like
history or math or anything else. Like
people were just like shocked about it
and we went on lockdown. Yeah, they
immediately went on lockdown. Parents
were trying to pick their kids up from
school because like this was like in the
middle of it, right? I mean,
like nobody knew what was going on. They
didn't know if this was going to be a
broader attack, if this was the
beginning of some kind of like Pearl
Harbor thing, right? I mean, nobody
knows what's going on and like you see
your kid that's not with you and you're
freaking out about it. So, you're going
to go get your kid. I remember I I think
I like
I don't remember exactly what it was for
me. I I don't think I really called my
parents or anything. I was just like,
you know, like I my mom picks me up from
school. She's like, "What did you do
today?" I'm like, "Nothing. There's like
some thing that happened, right? They
like hit a plane tower." She's like,
"Yeah, I saw that."
And that was about it, right? I mean, it
wasn't really too crazy. But yeah, even
the day after and the day after that,
people weren't really, you know, doing
anything other than just sitting around
talking about it. And that was it.
Everyone older than me joined the
military after 9/11. Yeah, I mean, well,
that was clearly that was the mindset,
right? Is that, you know, you're going
to join the military, you're going to go
over there, you're going to kill the
guys that did 9/11. Like that was the
entire concept. And you know, to maybe
an extent that happened. I mean, we did
get Osama bin Laden eventually. But
ultimately, I think that what's happened
is that we've also imported millions of
people into America that think America
deserved 9/11. So, in a way, we might
have won the battle, but I think we lost
the war. And we've allowed ourselves to
be you know, basically infiltrated by a
huge contingency of people that support
9/11, that rationalize 9/11, that
justify 9/11, that encourage 9/11, and
that encourage groups that if they had
their way, there'd be a 9/11 every
single day. So, to me, whenever I see
people going like, "Oh my god, this is
like, you know, we had this bit massive
war
and and everything." I think it was a a
huge his I mean, again, like that's it's
only one example, right? There's a lot
of other examples.
So, a Muslim extremist is a mayor of New
York City. I think we lost the war.
Well, it's because people are unwilling
to call out very clearly that this is a
problem with like, I mean, just it is a
it is a violent massive problem. And
anybody who supports anything like 9/11
should not be in the country.
Like it's just that simple. Like if you
can't unequivocally condemn this, and
you have to preposition it behind, "Oh,
well, look at all the people in the
Middle East that got killed." They
wouldn't have gotten killed if 9/11
didn't happen.
9/11 should have never happened.
And a lot of those people, like people
in Palestine were cheering for 9/11.
Like I don't know if I can pull up a
clip of this or not, but like the day
after 9/11, you could see the streets of
Palestine were happy and gleeful because
9/11 happened.
It's common sense. Yes, definitely. Mad
Money used it as another excuse to talk
about his mom being a victim of racism
after 9/11. Why did the USA join the
sand war? Is it Israel or portals? I
mean, I think that really
the reality is that
extremist Islam poses an existential
threat to American and Western culture.
This is just the reality.
Like there there can't be a coexistence
with extremist radical fundamentalist
Islamists like the Taliban, ISIS,
Al-Qaeda,
any of these groups, right? This
one, yeah, I'm not sure if I can find
it. Were people outside of the US happy
that 9/11 happened? Because they blame
the US for their problems. That's why.
It's actually just really simple.
Yeah, here you go. Flashback,
Palestinians celebrate the fall of the
World Trade Center towers in 2001.
>> atmosphere. The V sign for victory being
displayed
in East Jerusalem today among jubilant
Palestinians that the United States had
been subject to this attack. What are we
to make of that, Jennifer? Are we to
Yasser Arafat may issue this
condemnation. Look at this. We're seeing
people applauding, clapping, smiling,
happy to to know that thousands of
Americans have died in this sneak
attack. And there you see a V for
victory sign held up to the camera. What
are we to make of that and what are we
to make of what
about what
Yasser Arafat said today?
>> It's really bad.
>> The United States blamed by some
Palestinians for its ongoing support as
it is seen of Israel in this conflict in
this Middle Eastern conflict.
>> Uh-huh.
>> While some Palestinians were taking to
the streets in apparent celebration, one
youth was quoted as saying as he
received a sweet sweets handed around in
celebration, this is a suite from Osama
bin Laden, he said.
>> Back to you.
>> Hap Tausend, thanks very much. We have
some video tape, I understand, that
we're going to show you from the West
Bank.
>> And you can see this is like right
around the exact same time.
>> terror attacks in the United States.
How apparently Palestinians took to the
streets saying God is great. People were
throwing candies.
>> Can it be taken out of context? Did they
interview anyone? What do you think?
>> The US
>> What do you think, man?
>> has become increasingly increasingly
unpopular, particularly in the West Bank
and Gaza Strip, because
>> That's crazy.
>> feel that the US government [music]
>> Hamas celebrating, just regular
Palestinians? I have no idea. There's a
lot of them.
>> And now while Abdel Fattah, wearing
[music] a long black black dress, three
>> It's a gift from bin Laden?
>> Actually, that's a woman, pardon me,
saying she was happy because, quote,
"America is the head of the snake.
America always stands by
>> America is the head of the snake.
>> against us." Meanwhile, Yasser Arafat
emerged to speak with reporters.
>> That's amazing, isn't it?
And now these people are in America
trying to get Americans to support them
after they were celebrating 9/11.
Yeah, I don't know, guys. I don't think
so.
Yeah, that's that's too much, right? And
yeah, people and people do support them
because again, we have a we have allowed
a huge contingency of these people to
come into the country.
And it should have never happened.
It should have never happened, and it's
not too late to undo it as well.
Like we can send a lot of these people
back now. We can do this. You just
change the rules, you have the military
and the National Guard remove them,
seize their assets on the way out, and
then that's it. They're gone. They're
going back. It won't happen. It can
happen, though. It can like
theoretically we could do this.
It's just that not enough people are
willing to do that. It's because
students now don't know about 9/11.
Yeah, but think about why they're not
being taught about 9/11. They're not
being taught about 9/11 because the
institutions that run education are
ideologically captured and they don't
want to provide like this is this is a
big problem with uh you know, public
education and American education is that
American and public education is
weighted in a way that it looks at all
the atrocities and bad actions of
America the bad actions of like let's
say
you know, Europe or something like that,
but it doesn't it doesn't contextualize
the bad actions of the rest of the world
and what led to those bad actions. So, I
think that's really the main problem is
that like the education system is built
entirely around establishing an original
sin on the American people collectively
rather than looking at why these things
happened. Like
the Crusades for example were defensive.
They were a response to encroachment
from people from the Middle East. It's
not like that the Pope just decided
let's just do this one day, but the
first Crusades were as a response to
that. If they had never done that, it
would have never happened. So, and uh we
need another. I mean again, I don't even
I don't want to this is my mindset. I
don't want another Crusade. I don't want
a another war. I don't want any of this.
I want them to stay over there. I want
us to stay over here. They can visit.
The ones that are normal can visit and
the ones of us that are normal can visit
them and we can have a shared
appreciation for each other's culture
from a distance.
That's my mindset.
That's what I think.
Saying stuff like this riled people up.
Let me see it.
So, Ron says the real victim of 9/11
Oh, what is this?
>> I want to use this moment to speak to
the Muslims of New York City.
>> I bet.
>> [clears throat]
>> I want to speak to the memory of my
aunt.
>> Mhm.
Yeah.
>> Who stopped taking the subway after
September 11th because she did not feel
safe in her hijab.
>> Yeah.
>> I want to use this moment
>> Apparently this story was fake, too, by
the way. The whole thing was fake.
Everything about it was fake. And this
is President Bush 6 days after the
attack. Let me see it.
>> That's not what Islam is all about.
>> Mhm.
>> Islam is peace.
These terrorists
>> Mhm.
>> don't represent peace.
>> No, they don't.
>> evil and war.
When we think of Islam, we think of a
faith that brings comfort to a billion
people around the world.
Billions of people
find comfort
and solace
and peace.
>> Mhm.
>> Bro, this is the
this part of the strat faith that want
to rule over us once Islam is more
power, they'll rule us by the sword.
This is my mindset. I think that in the
same way that, you know, Saudi Arabia
doesn't accept the idea of not becoming
a Islamic country or Turkey doesn't
accept the idea of not becoming an
Islamic country, I think that we should
we should make a focus around making
America a Christian country. Uh this is
just the reality. Um I don't have a
problem with Muslims living here. I
don't think they have a problem with
clearly a lot of Christians living
there. At least maybe they do. It
depends. I bet there's probably a
spectrum. But ultimately
this is the dominant culture and this is
the dominant religion.
And I don't want people from other parts
of the country and other actually
country, other parts of the world coming
over to America and changing our culture
and changing and trying to insert their
own culture into it because I think
fundamentally the way that they do
things over in the Middle East is not
compatible with the way that we do
things here in America. It's not.
Whether it comes down to women's rights,
whether it goes down to freedom of
speech, whether it goes down to freedom
of religion. It just doesn't work. So,
there has to be a predominant culture
and I think over there it's Islam and
over here it needs to be Christianity.
And I think that needs to be stated and
it needs to be clear. And a lot of
Americans don't want to say that. They
don't want to say that because they
think that oh, well, you're not supposed
to say this. The reality is that all of
the founding fathers agree with this.
They even said it. Like I talked about
this earlier with John Adams. So,
and I want us to get what is this here?
And my name Trump is decapitation events
for us Canadians. I don't know about
that. They want to win the war by
religion dominion like civilization.
Well, it just makes sense that if there
are more people of a certain religion
that that religion becomes the dominant
force. There's like so a good example is
India. India is like I think it's 2030
maybe 7030
Islamic versus Hindu and guess what the
dominant force in India is? It's Hindu.
And it's a Hindu country. They do things
off of Hindu customs and that's the way
that they do things. There's there and
and you can have another religion. You
can believe whatever you want, but this
is the
This is the cohesive structure in which
the society of India is built around.
And I think that too many Americans are
afraid to acknowledge this reality with
the United States. I'm an atheist and I
agree with you. I'm an agnostic
personally. Like I don't have any
animosity really towards any of the
religions specifically. Like I think
that Christianity's done bad things, you
know, Islam's done bad things, Hinduism
has done bad things, Judaism's done bad
things. Ultimately, I think religion is
kind of like a tool and if you use a
tool in a way that can hurt people, then
that's bad. [music] And if you use the
tool in a way that enriches and makes
your life better, that's good. But at a
certain place, I think that like, you
know, if you're at a farm, you don't
want to bring a I don't know, like what
what what tool do you not use at a farm?
I'd have to really think this out as an
analogy. I I I haven't really thought
about it a whole lot. Right? But like if
you're at a blacksmith, you're not going
to bring a hoe, right? Like if you're a
blacksmith, you're not going to bring a
a rake to a blacksmith shop. So at the
end of the day, what I'm saying is that
we're black blacksmith shop and we don't
we don't need a lot of these other
tools, right? We have one specific thing
and that's the way it is.
And agnostic is not on the spectrum of
theism and atheism, it's a different
dimension. You can be agnostic theist or
agnostic atheist. I don't want to argue
about the the definitions. It it's not
really important to me.
My point is that I don't know if there's
a god or not and I don't think that any
human being has the capacity to perceive
that. That's generally what my opinion
is, but I do also think that religion is
a necessary cohesive force for societal,
you know, like
like not friction. Like tranquility.
I think you need religion.
So that's it. And while moderate Muslims
speak out after 9/11, it's clear
extremists are the norm. Even now it
seems like moderate Muslims still exist.
Well, probably because they get attacked
and threatened. I think that's one
reason. And yeah, I'm sure a lot of them
aren't extremists. Anybody who thinks
like this though, this is the way I look
at it, is that anybody who's trying to
reframe 9/11 as, you know, a tragedy for
the Middle East or anything like that,
go to the Middle East and stay there.
Stay there and don't come back. I am so
sick of these people in the country. I
don't want them here. I don't think
anybody wants them here. And I think
that it should be more outspoken that
this is not acceptable. Like I don't
want to deal with this. Like why are we
dealing with this? Why are we putting up
with this? So,
if religion is the glue for society,
yeah, I mean you need I think that the
society needs religion. That's my point,
right? They need religion.
Mhm.
Cohesion relies religion. Yeah, religion
made humans into civilized especially
Christianity.
Well, my point is that all of the 9/11
stuff that's happened. I mean this this
was like it was really really bad never
had happened. I remember this quite
well. And seeing all the images and
everything. And there's a big difference
too, by the way. There's a really big
difference between people that are
making jokes about 9/11. Like I've made
so many jokes about 9/11. And I will
continue to make jokes about 9/11 just
because I like dark humor. But the
difference is that the other people that
are making jokes about 9/11 are not
joking around. They're normalizing
like minimizing its influence because
they don't want it to be a negative
social thing for them. That's it.
Yeah, but you're joking. Yeah, yeah, the
difference is that I'm joking whenever I
make a joke about 9/11. Whereas these
other people are like tongue-in-cheek
supporting it. And I think that's really
what the scary and bad thing is, right?
And uh is this what it was?
Yeah, I don't remember hardly any of
this. This is a long ass time ago as I
said.
>> [applause]
>> Ladies and gentlemen, this is a
difficult moment for America.
>> Yeah, I remember he was in a school when
it happened.
>> Unfortunately, we'll be going back to
Washington after my remarks.
Secretary Rod Paige, with the Governor,
We'll take the podium [clears throat] to
discuss education.
I do want to thank the folks here at uh
at the Booker Elementary School for the
hospitality.
Uh today we've had a national tragedy.
Two airplanes
>> Mhm.
>> have crashed into the World Trade Center
in an apparent terrorist attack on our
country.
>> Yeah, down in front.
>> I have spoken to the
government
>> to the Governor of New York.
>> It's my fourth birthday.
>> He has the FBI.
And I've ordered that the full resources
of the federal government
go to help the victims and their
families.
>> It is
>> We will conduct a
to hunt down
and to find those folks
who committed this act.
>> It's actually crazy like being So, I'm
36, right? So, I was born in 1990. So,
whenever I was growing up, obviously
there was conversation all the time
about how technology is going to change
everything, and then the internet came
in, which was like a total paradigm
shift, and people were like, "Oh my god,
what the is this?" Then Y2K is
going to happen, which was like this
massive uh global conspiracy theory that
all the tech systems were going to like
explode and stop working whenever the
millennium happened for the year 2000.
And then right after that, you had 9/11.
And then after that, you had, you know,
this you know, the war in uh in
Afghanistan, and then in Iraq, and then
in Syria, and everywhere else,
right? Then you have the 2008 crash of
the economy. Then Obama gets elected
president. Then, you know, after that
there's a massive recession that goes on
for like 2 or 3 years. Finally, that
kind of begins to settle.
And doesn't even really settle. Things
are worse before than it was after, or
sorry, that
things are worse after than it was
before. And then, uh you know, then you
start getting like all this like that's
whenever they started really putting
like a lot of messaging in like TV shows
and movies and stuff.
Like weird uh subversive type messaging.
Then yeah, anthrax as well.
Like it's like whenever I see people
that are around my age that have like a
bunch of anxiety and stress. Oh, oh, let
me let me finish though. Let me finish.
So then after that, then Trump becomes
president. And whether you like Trump or
not, you got to admit that was a big
deal. That was a huge
deal, Trump getting elected, right? This
happens and then finally, okay, well,
now things are starting to get normal.
All right, Trump is elected, things
aren't as crazy as we thought it COVID.
Immediately you get COVID. And now
COVID's happening and then right
whenever COVID's ending, now AI's
replacing everybody and people are
discussing what the percentage chance is
on AI killing all humans. And that's
happening today.
This is what it's like to be my age in
America.
This is it.
I MEAN, HOLY GUYS.
God damn.
Really? Think about this. We're
sci-op'd? I mean, yes. And so you can't
make this up. So Epstein died
before COVID. He did.
And now women are Yeah, and now women
And and now we live in a world people
are supporting Hamas. They support 9/11.
We have
random terrorist supporters everywhere
in America. Women are collectively
finally being able to stand each other
stand over the political divide and
finally come to agreeance on one thing.
What's that one thing? Killing your
kids. Okay.
So there you go. It It's just
everything is bad.